Schein, Donald; Papers apap209
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- 1994, WMHT Internal Records (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 14)
- 1994, WMHT Long Range Plan (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 15)
- 1995, Correspondence (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 16)
- 1995, Day-Timer, 1995 January (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 17)
- 1995, Day-Timer, 1995 February (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 18)
- 1995, Day-Timer, 1995 March (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 19)
- 1995, Day-Timer, 1995 April (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 20)
- 1995, Day-Timer, 1995 May (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 21)
- 1995, Day-Timer, 1995 June (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 22)
- 1995, Day-Timer, 1995 July (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 23)
- 1995, Day-Timer, 1995 August (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 24)
- 1995, Day-Timer, 1995 September (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 25)
- 1995, Day-Timer, 1995 October (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 26)
- 1995, Day-Timer, 1995 November (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 27)
- 1995, Day-Timer, 1995 December (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 28)
- 1995, News Clippings on WMHT (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 29)
- 1995, Prelude, Program (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 30)
- 1995, WMHT Internal Records (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 31)
- 1996, News Clippings on WMHT (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 32)
- 1996, Prelude (Program) (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 33)
- 1996, WMHT Internal Records (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 34)
- 1997, News Clippings on WMHT (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 35)
- 1997, Notes (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 36)
- 1997, Prelude (Program) (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 37)
- 1998, News Clippings on WMHT (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 38)
- 1998, Prelude, Program (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 39)
- 1998, Station History (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 40)
- 1999, News Clippings on WMHT (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 41)
- 1999, Prelude, Program (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 42)
- 2000, Prelude, Program (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 43)
- 2001, Prelude, Program (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 44)
- 2002, Prelude/Outlook, Program (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 45)
- 2003, Outlook, Program (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 46)
- 2004, Outlook, Program (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 47)
- 2005, Outlook, Program (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 48)
- Educational Television/Public Broadcasting, Undated (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 49)
- News Clippings on WMHT, Undated (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 50)
- WMHT Internal Records, Undated (Box 38 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 51)
- MHCET Promotional Photographs, 1954-1956 (Box 39 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 1-6)
- Articles on MHCET Foreign Language Broadcasts, 1956 (Box 39 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 7)
- Producing Your Educational Television Program, MHCET Publication, 1961 (Box 39 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 8)
- WMHT Promotional Photographs, Contact Sheets and Negatives, 1961-1962 (Box 39 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 9)
- VHF Station Announcement Negatives, 1962? (Box 40 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 1)
- Family Photographs, Contact Sheets and Negatives, 1963 (Box 40 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 2)
- Aerial Photographs of Transmitter Site, 1970-1972 (Box 40 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 3)
- Contact Sheet and Negatives, Baltimore EEN Meeting, 1977 (Box 40 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 4)
- Family Photographs, 1980s? (Box 40 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 5)
- Negatives (Box 40 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 6-7)
- Promotional Photos, Loose (Box 40 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 8)
- Promotional Photos (Box 40 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 9-12)
- Promotional Photos, Loose (Box 41 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 1)
- Promotional Photos (Box 41 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 2-6)
- Promotional Photos, Loose, Mostly WMHT-FM? (Box 41 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 7)
- Promotional Photos (Box 41 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 8)
- Portrait Photographs, Various Individuals (Box 41 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 9)
- Promotional Photos, Station History (Box 41 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 10)
- Trustee Portraits (Box 41 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 11)
- Photographs, Executive Mansion, Albany, Fundraising Event?, 1960s? (Box 41 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 12)
- Contact Sheets and Negatives (Box 41 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 13-14)
- Contact Sheets and Negatives, Loose (Box 41 (Donald Schein Papers), Folder 15)